ukmail.com 2010-12-11

# UK Mail | Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY 

This page states our Privacy Policy for our Website located at [www.ukmail.com](http://www.businesspost.com/) (the “Website”).

**General**  
UK Mail facilitates the delivery of important letters, parcels and documents. As such, personal information will be required from you if you wish to use our Website for purposes including the use of our online credit card payment facility.   
Your privacy is important to us. This privacy policy is intended to give you confidence in the privacy and security of the personal information we obtain from you whether you are merely visiting our Website, or are making a payment using our online credit card facility. However, please note that we are not responsible for any use of your personal information in respect of third party websites that may be accessed via this Website. You will therefore need to review the privacy policy of any third party websites that you use.

**Collection of Personal Information  
** When you access our Website, cookie information pages you have requested and your IP address may be recorded by us and/or third parties from your browser as set out in this policy http://www.ukmail.com/privacy.html.  
If you use this Website you may be asked for personally identifiable information such as your name and address. By giving us such information you will need to consent to our using it in the manner described in this policy. On-line credit and debit card payments to UK Mail are made through a third party provider and will require us to share personal information with Close Credit Management Limited. It is important that you review their Privacy Policy at Close Credit Management Limited’s website,www.paicheck.com before using the online payment facility.  
You may withdraw your consent at any time by emailing us at [marketing@ukmail.com](mailto:marketing@ukmail.com)  

**Use of Personal Information  
** We may use your information to provide access to privileged areas of the Website, personalise your visit to our Website, to enable us to review, develop and improve the products, services, and special offers we provide online, as well as to administer any payment request that you may wish to make.   
We may occasionally carry out market research and send you details of services and offers that we think will be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive such information, please email us at [marketing@ukmail.com](mailto:marketing@ukmail.com)

**Disclosure of Personal Information  
** We may provide information about you to employees and agents of UK Mail to administer any accounts, products and services provided to you by UK Mail.

We will not disclose your personal information to any third party unless you have consented to such disclosure or where we are required to do so by law. Should you breach our terms and conditions or terms of use or if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, we may disclose your information to a relevant authority. This may include exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.  
Any disclosure of personal information will be strictly controlled and made fully in accordance with current UK legislation, in particular the UK Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act). For the purpose of the Act, the data controller is UK Mail Group PLC, Express House, 464 Berkshire Avenue, Slough, Berkshire, SL1 4PL. 

**Right to access your Personal Information  
** The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. You can obtain access to your personal information held by us by sending a cheque for £10 (to cover administration costs for collating this information), made payable to "UK Mail Group PLC", to: Data Protection Officer, UK Mail Group PLC, Express House, 464 Berkshire Avenue, Slough, Berkshire, SL1 4PL. 

**Cookies  
** We may create and access cookies (a piece of information like a "tag" which is stored on your computer and allows us to identify if you have visited the Website before) on your PC. Third party advertisers may also create and access cookies, which will be subject to their privacy policies - we accept no responsibility or liability for the use of such third parties' cookies. If you do not wish cookies to be placed on your PC, then they can be disabled in your web browser. The option to do so is normally found in your browser's "security settings" section. However, please note, permanently disabling cookies in your browser may hinder your use of our Website as well as other websites and interactive services.

**Security  
** At UK Mail we take security very seriously including the use of the online credit card payment facility operated by Close Credit Management Ltd. Your browser will go into secure mode before you enter any payment details. You can check that you are making such payments in a secure environment by looking for either a locked padlock or a key icon in the grey bar at the bottom of your screen or when the address bar goes green.

Being in 'secure mode' means that all of your details are encrypted to help keep them secure. Encryption creates billions of code combinations to protect each transaction made on our Website, so your card details cannot be viewed by anyone else using the Internet.  
No credit or debit card details are stored on our servers once your initial payment has been processed. They are stored securely with Close Credit Management Ltd. Once on their systems, all sensitive data is secured using internationally recognised 256-bit encryption standards. The encryption keys are held on state-of-the-art, tamper proof systems in the same family as those used to secure VeriSign's Global Root certificate, making them all but impossible to extract. The data they hold is extremely secure and they are regularly audited by the banks and banking authorities to ensure it remains so.

If you have any further concerns about security, please email our Customer Service team at   
[marketing@ukmail.com](mailto:marketing@ukmail.com) or call our Customer Service team on 08451 552 552. 

**Policy Changes  
** Changes in this policy will be posted on our Website. You are advised to check our Website regularly to view our most recent privacy policy.
